nextpowerup.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | NextPowerUp

We respect your privacy and are committed to protect the privacy and confidentiality of personal data we collect when you use our website. This Privacy Policy describes the ways we collect information from and about you, and what we do with the information, so that you may decide whether or not to provide information to us.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS DESCRIBED HEREIN AND ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.

## 1\. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies to all information (including, personal information) collected through the Website. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term "visitor" includes visitors to the Website, whether you upload information to the Website, download it, or are merely visiting the Website; the term "personal information" means information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Website, or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information, and we may share aggregate data about our users with third parties for various purposes. You can choose not to provide certain information when using the Website but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of its features.

## 2\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### Active Collection of Information

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit the Website. We may collect certain information that you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name, email address, user name, and telephone number when you register, set up an account or contact us by e-mail.

### Passive Collection of Information

When you visit the Website, some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. Such information includes your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your usage and activity on the Site.

### Online Mediums Reminder

Chat rooms, forums, blogs and/or news groups ("Online Mediums") may be available. Any information that you disclose in the Online Mediums becomes public information. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal identifiable information. We reserve the right to remove or edit any posting that we find is vulgar or inappropriate.

### Web Visit

You may visit our Websites in any of the following ways:

  * by using your browser to navigate to our Website
  * by viewing an advertisement displayed on a third party website that is served content by our web server
  * by viewing an email that is served content by our or a third party web server

When you visit our Website, our server logs your IP address (unique network addresses), the time and duration of your visit, and the time and duration of the pages on our website you view. If you arrive at our website by clicking a paid advertisement (including a paid search engine result) or a link in an email, then we will capture information that tracks your visit from that link. If you arrive at our Website by clicking a non-paid source, such as link in a non-paid search engine result or an unsponsored link on another website, we may capture information that tracks your visit from that source, to the extent we are able to do so. We may also capture information about your computer system, such as your browser type and operating system.

We will likely place a cookie on your hard drive during the web visit. A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that we use to help us identify the number of unique visitors to our Website, whether or not those visitors are repeat visitors, and the source of the visits. Cookies cannot be executed as code or used to deliver a virus. Other servers cannot read them and personal information cannot be gathered from them. They are simply an identifier shared between you and us to allow us to improve the services we offer to you through our Website. If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your computer, then they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser's "security settings" section. However, please note, permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your use of our Website as well as other websites and interactive services.

A web beacon, also known as a web bug, is a small graphic (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel), that might be embedded in a web advertisement, email, or page on our web site, but is invisible to you. When you view a page on our web site, an email or an advertisement your web browser will request the web beacon from a web server, which in turn will set a cookie in your web browser containing a unique identifier. This unique identifier will be linked to log information that is used to track your movements on our web site in order to determine the effectiveness of content and advertising campaigns.

We do not collect personal information about you as part of a web visit, but web visit information may be tied to other information (including personal information) we collect from you via chat, web forms, and the other means we describe in this Privacy Policy.

Our advertising agencies may also use web beacons and cookies to track your activity on our website originating from the advertisement. However, we will not provide your personal information to our advertising agencies. Our advertising agencies maintain their own privacy policies, and you should also review those.

## Links to other websites

We may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. The privacy practices of those sites may differ from our practices and are not controlled by us and covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not make any representations about third-party websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before submitting your personal data.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection

Our services are not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

## 3\. WHAT DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION FOR?

Contact and other Personal Information. We use visitor information to send information about our site to visitors and to get in touch with them when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of the Website. We may use your information to communicate with you, provide access to secure areas of the Website, recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you, to personalize your visit to our Website, and to enable us to review develop and continually improve the information we provide online. We also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

We use web visit information to measure interest in and develop our web pages and marketing plans, customize the content you view on your web visits based on your activity on past visits, and administer our Website.

We use the visitor's IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Websites.  
We use cookies to help us recognize visitors as unique visitors (just a number) when they return to our websites. For example, if there are 1,000 visits to our website on a certain day, we can use cookies to discover how many of those visits were made via the same browser (same visitor). We may also use the cookie to discover whether a certain visitor has visited our site more than once, and the source for each visit. We also use cookies to: allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interest; avoid showing visitors the same advertisements repeatedly; compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our Website (we cannot identify visitors personally in this way); count the number of anonymous users of our sites.  
We use web beacons to count the number of times that our advertisements and web-based email content are viewed. We combine web beacon information with cookies to track activity on our website originating from advertisements and web-based email content.

Information provided to us via telephone calls, chat, email, web forms and other communications. We use this information to correspond with you.

## 4\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information we gather is for internal use only and will not authorize the release of this information to anyone outside (except to third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf but in such event personal information will only be shared to the extent reasonably necessary to perform their functions and they will not be authorized to use it for any other function), unless you have consented to such disclosure.

Should you breach our Website Terms of Use, or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, we may disclose your information to a relevant authority. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. In particular, we may release the information we collect to third parties when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce our legal rights, to protect the rights and safety of others, or to assist with industry efforts to control fraud, spam or other undesirable conduct.

## 5\. YOUR CHOICES ABOUT RECEIVING E-MAIL and OPTING OUT OF COMMUNICATIONS

We give you an opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving communications from us or opting-out of personal data being disclosed to third parties for a purpose incompatible with the purpose for which it was originally collected (except for meeting applicable legal requirements or permitting third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf as described in Section 4 of this Privacy Policy), including your opting out of receiving future marketing mailings.

We will not use your contact information to correspond with you about our services if you ask us not to. Please send your request to admin@nextpowerup.com. Please note that it may take up to ten days to remove your contact information from our marketing communications lists, so you may receive correspondence from us for a short time after you make your request.

## 6\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use various security measures to protect your personal information (including, preventing the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal information). We store information you provide to us on a computer system located in a controlled facility with a limited access.

If you use a password on the Website, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please notify us immediately.

## 7\. RIGHT TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you believe that any personal information we have about you is incorrect, or is, has been, or might be used inappropriately, please contact us at admin@nextpowerup.com and we will take steps to correct or delete the information, or restrict its use, as appropriate.

## 8\. INQUIRIES OR COMPLAINTS

If you have a question or complaint about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us at admin@nextpowerup.com.

## 9\. CHANGES

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes; however, we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past without your prior consent. This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 20, 2015.
